<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Three Good Things</title>
    <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/"></link>
    <updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Three Good Things</name>
        <uri>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/</uri>
    </author>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-07-13</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-07-13</id>
        <published>2023-07-13T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner and I went to the theatre for their birthday. It was a comedy, one of those &amp;#34;it&amp;#39;s a play but it all goes a bit weird&amp;#34; things. I honestly didn&amp;#39;t expect to like it as much as I did 🎭&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;We went to a really great restaurant afterwards and had some excellent food and wine 🍷&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got my iPod working with Libre.FM and music logging and everything! There&amp;#39;s still some issues with syncing music to the device but it&amp;#39;s all very solvable 📻&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-07-12</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-07-12</id>
        <published>2023-07-12T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-07-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got a charging cable for my iPod, so hopefully I can get back to using that as my main music driver more regularly 🎧&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I skated to the shops and the cool coffee shop nearby to pick up some beans. I am loving getting back into skateboarding and how closely cruising maps to carving in feeling on my feet 🛹&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got the emoji picker on Linux Mint working (as you can tell 😅) — and just generally feeling more comfy in my computer and tech space again. I&amp;#39;ve had a long time of my only interaction with technology being either my work laptop(s) or my phone. It&amp;#39;s easy to forget how fucking good a personal computer is 🖥️&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-07-11</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-07-11</id>
        <published>2023-07-11T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-07-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I recorded a podcast for my work about queer history, very proud of the content I put into it and excited to see the outcome 🎙️&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I replaced the inner tube on my bike and went for a ride to a nearby quiet, green place for lunch 🌿&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I chatted on the phone with my friend while we both got some work done — love to &amp;#34;co-work&amp;#34; 💻&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-07-10</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-07-10</id>
        <published>2023-07-10T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-07-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Skated to the shops to get lunch today and felt pretty confident in it — although, I did lose the cross pendant I made 😅&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner and I had a gorgeous pesto macaroni cheese for dinner.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went for the first &lt;a href=&#34;/runs/&#34;&gt;run&lt;/a&gt; of my marathon training plan. It was really, really tough but I feel good for having finished it. I&amp;#39;m proud of myself.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-07-09</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-07-09</id>
        <published>2023-07-09T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-07-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Church today was welcomed. The worship music was awesome and there were a tonne of interesting questions and conversations coming up in the preach on John 6.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner and I went to a market and ate momo. I had a chat with the guy running the stall about spiciness.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I wrote a &lt;a href=&#34;/color/&#34;&gt;color of the day&lt;/a&gt; thing for the website, just a neat little friend.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-07-08</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-07-08</id>
        <published>2023-07-08T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-07-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner and I redid our undercuts, love that DIY freshness!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I wrote some golang to implement this very thing you&amp;#39;re reading! It&amp;#39;s a super simple spec for an ordered list of three items, combined with a template — and it works!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Big depression-y day today so I stayed in and watched Treasure Planet with the partner, it was nice. Not the massive fun-filled evening I had planned, but I think it&amp;#39;s what I needed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-07-07</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-07-07</id>
        <published>2023-07-07T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-07-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went to a WatchHouse for coffee, which was just superb. So peachy and fruity.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I made a really delicious satay tofu and pasta dish.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner and I hung out, watched some TV and ate ice cream. Just a relaxed chill night.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-07-06</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-07-06</id>
        <published>2023-07-06T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-07-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner and I went to Kew Gardens via a Gail&amp;#39;s and had some of the most delicious feta and sesame seed parcels — they seem so makeable.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Kew was gorgeous, and I&amp;#39;m so proud of my partner for going up on the treetop walkway which I know was absolutely terrifying for them.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;A few of us went out for dinner at a taqueria then went to a great cocktail bar in Soho.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-07-05</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-07-05</id>
        <published>2023-07-05T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-07-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had a really lovely call with my friend which I think both of us needed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I picked up my partner&amp;#39;s birthday tart from the bakery, absolutely gorgeous.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner made the most delicious mushroom-y pasta for dinner.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-07-04</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-07-04</id>
        <published>2023-07-04T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-07-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Managed to skate to the shops and back with no ankle problems!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Girlfriend and I watched the second episode of Dead Ringers, as well as Ze Frank videos.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I cooked arepas again for myself and girlfriend, and they turned out really good!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-07-03</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-07-03</id>
        <published>2023-07-03T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-07-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had a very sudden and bad depressive moment, but my partner stayed with me while I worked through it. I&amp;#39;m so glad they&amp;#39;re in my life.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner got out their crochet hook and I started learning based on what someone had told me at church camp. Loving it so far!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had scrambled eggs on a bagel with some hot sauce for breakfast.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-07-02</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-07-02</id>
        <published>2023-07-02T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-07-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Baptisms were so beautiful. Everyone picked a song that we all song together, then prayed for them before they got dunked. One of the most powerfully emotional, spiritual and community-affirming things I&amp;#39;ve been part of.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;On the train home a few of us had chats about city planning, urban renewal and how to improve our own environments a bit more.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner and I got pizza and watched the pizza Chef&amp;#39;s Table — which is about right for us.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-07-01</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-07-01</id>
        <published>2023-07-01T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-07-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I woke up and made some coffee, then went for a walk around the grounds. This whole estate is absolutely gorgeous.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Morning worship was super interesting, we worked together to build a table out of a table. A couple of us went foraging for greenery to put in it!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;A group of us went for a lovely walk together through the countryside, and I had a really meaningful chat about faith with one of the other people there.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-06-30</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-06-30</id>
        <published>2023-06-30T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner and I went out to lunch, I had charred hispi cabbage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got packed and went away with my church for the weekend. Got there safely, listening to some TRS Presents the Bible.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had some pretty lovely chats with church folks, and we played Monopoly Deal.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-06-29</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-06-29</id>
        <published>2023-06-29T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Did some spin bike, it felt good to get back to working out after injury times.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Girlfriend and I went to see Asteroid City, what a banger!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Started working through SICP again, which is always fun.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-06-28</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-06-28</id>
        <published>2023-06-28T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Spoke to my friend on the phone.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Did some D&amp;amp;D planning.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Watched Neptune Frost, cool flick.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-06-27</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-06-27</id>
        <published>2023-06-27T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had leftover arepas fried with the toppings for lunch which was great.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went to girlfriend&amp;#39;s place for dinner and we cooked something from a recipe book she got me.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;We played a couple of games of Netrunner, as well as Dominion which I hadn&amp;#39;t played in forever.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-06-26</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-06-26</id>
        <published>2023-06-26T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Chatted to one of my work colleagues for a bit over teams, I miss just shooting shit with people in the office.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Someone sent through questions for a potential podcast appearance I might be doing, about LGBTQ+ history!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I made arepas for dinner, which I&amp;#39;ve never done before — and roasted my own red peppers, another new thing!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-06-21</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-06-21</id>
        <published>2023-06-21T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I gave myself a tattoo!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Listened to a Christian metalcore playlist that honestly went off.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I injured my ankle on holiday, but it&amp;#39;s already feeling a bit better.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-06-12</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-06-12</id>
        <published>2023-06-12T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went to the shopping mall and bought bikinis, I feel so hot!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went for a walk in a park nearby and got caught in a thunderstorm downpour, which was a gorgeous moment in the rawness of nature.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner and I made a picnic dinner together.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-06-11</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-06-11</id>
        <published>2023-06-11T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Church was lovely. We did a sort of adjusted examen, then the sermon was on Numbers 5:11-29 which no-one was happy with — but it led to some interesting chats.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I hung out with someone from church, we watched a brass band play in the park.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner and I explored the island in Stardew! Never made it this far before.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-06-10</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-06-10</id>
        <published>2023-06-10T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I tried boxing for the first time — very challenging and different to what I&amp;#39;m used to, but super fun.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Girlfriend and I had a date to see Reality, which was absolutely fantastic.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;We cooked burgers together, they turned out great.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-06-09</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-06-09</id>
        <published>2023-06-09T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner was home from work today so we hung out during my breaks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;We went out to a local pizza place and I &lt;i&gt;once again&lt;/i&gt; got a compliment on my dress!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;We chilled out, had a beer and played Stardew for the rest of the evening.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-06-08</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-06-08</id>
        <published>2023-06-08T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I cut the sleeves off my Crab Museum t-shirt, some gay excellence there.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got everything ticked off of my work todo list ahead of holidays.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner made a lovely carbonara-style dish.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-06-07</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-06-07</id>
        <published>2023-06-07T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Wore my new black dress out to get coffee, and the barista gave me a little compliment!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I made a really lovely aubergine and pecorino pasta sauce with tagliatelle for dinner.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Partner and I went for a walk together in the evening and then played Stardew Valley, so lovely.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-06-06</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-06-06</id>
        <published>2023-06-06T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Bought a cute black linen dress, perfect for summer.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Finished Harrow the Ninth — it was amazing, very interested to see where the series goes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got my laser redone, which is going to help with things.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-06-05</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-06-05</id>
        <published>2023-06-05T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went skateboarding and did some kick-turns on a slope — frontside &amp;amp; backside!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Girlfriend and I went to the new Spiderverse film, it was awesome!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;My partner showed me a lidocaine-based mouthwash thing that was incredibly helpful with my mouth ulcer. I have had those whenever I&amp;#39;ve been sick, like, my whole life — gamechanger!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-03-08</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-03-08</id>
        <published>2023-03-08T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-03-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I worked from a cute little cafe near my partner&amp;#39;s place. I had a couple of espressos and a vegan croissant, and was surrounded by mums, babies and dogs — a pretty lovely way to work!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had a date with my girlfriend, she made some really delicious dinner and we rewatched &lt;i&gt;John Wick&lt;/i&gt; before the new one comes out.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got a &lt;a href=&#34;https://alysvintagecameraalley.com/2020/01/19/the-bell-howell-canon-dial-35/&#34;&gt;Bell &amp;amp; Howell Dial 35&lt;/a&gt; loaded with film — and hopefully working? Guess we&amp;#39;ll find out! The shutter and aperture controls seem to be working correctly, although the light meter is busted. But I&amp;#39;m used to shooting fully manual by now.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-03-07</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-03-07</id>
        <published>2023-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got lunch with a friend in the city. I hadn&amp;#39;t seen her in ages, and it was really lovely to just catch up about each other&amp;#39;s lives.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I made pizza with my partner and helped them move some furniture around the place before our move.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;We watched &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Saved!&#34;&gt;&lt;i&gt;Saved!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt; , which was hilarious and a cool teen flick. Definitely some jokes that didn&amp;#39;t age well, but overall I feel like its heart was in the right place.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-03-06</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-03-06</id>
        <published>2023-03-06T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-03-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.freshrss.org/&#34;&gt;FreshRSS&lt;/a&gt; working and &lt;a href=&#34;https://rss.hd-dn.com&#34;&gt;set up on my domain&lt;/a&gt; , which is cool and interesting. I&amp;#39;m going to be looking for more RSS feeds to follow, recommendations welcome!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went for a photo walk, mostly taking pictures of churches and other buildings. They came out really beautifully — this was the first roll from an Olympus XA that I hadn&amp;#39;t tested yet.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;My girlfriend and I went on a date to see the new Antman movie, which was visually pretty spectacular — although I think the last 4 movies I&amp;#39;ve seen from Disney have been about fathers struggling to relate to their kids...&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-03-05</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-03-05</id>
        <published>2023-03-05T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-03-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went for breakfast with my partner at a cute vegan cafe, we had a &amp;#34;salmon&amp;#34; bagel and some pancakes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got lunch with my family and my girlfriend. It was the first time they&amp;#39;d all met, and it went really well — the food was great too.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went to see &lt;i&gt;Cocaine Bear&lt;/i&gt;, which was pretty much exactly what I was expecting.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-03-04</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-03-04</id>
        <published>2023-03-04T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-03-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I made a really lovely cup of pourover coffee using some &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.argyllcoffee.co.uk/&#34;&gt;beans&lt;/a&gt; I got for Christmas.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went to a muay thai class which was great, super fun and nice to go for a drink with them all after.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got my undercut refreshed, had a good chat with my barber and picked up a &lt;a href=&#34;https://cargocollective.com/modernqueers&#34;&gt;queer zine&lt;/a&gt; while I was there.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2023-03-03</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2023-03-03</id>
        <published>2023-03-03T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-03-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I am leading on some internal work at my day-job, which is super exciting!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;My partner and I cooked kung pao cauliflower and Sichuan aubergines from the book &lt;i&gt;East&lt;/i&gt; by &lt;a href=&#34;https://meerasodha.com/&#34;&gt;Meera Sodha&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I listened to &lt;a href=&#34;https://leftatlondon.bandcamp.com/&#34;&gt;Left At London&amp;#39;s&lt;/a&gt; Shrek rave DJ set, which is about as chaotic as I expected.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-11-02</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-11-02</id>
        <published>2022-11-02T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-11-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went bouldering again! My hands are shredded a bit but it was really good fun!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Great day at work today, I went into the office and was very productive. Made good progress on a couple things and got lunch with one of my colleagues.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a lovely phone call with my mum.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-11-01</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-11-01</id>
        <published>2022-11-01T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-11-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went to the opening of a photography exhibition, which was wonderful. Beautiful pictures, some utterly devastating.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Good spin bike session. I&amp;#39;m trying to do more exercise at the moment, and it&amp;#39;s definitely helping with my mood.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a really lovely dinner with someone I&amp;#39;m dating at a Thai restaurant.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-31</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-31</id>
        <published>2022-10-31T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went bouldering today! Was really fun, but my hands are kind of tired now! Definitely going to go again.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Rewatched Jennifer&amp;#39;s Body for Hallowe&amp;#39;en: fuck me that&amp;#39;s a good movie!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had dinner with someone I&amp;#39;m dating, which was really sweet, and a glass of sparkling wine to celebrate.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-30</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-30</id>
        <published>2022-10-30T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went and got brunch with my friend and someone I&amp;#39;m dating, lovely start to a Sunday.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;We went to the cinema to see The Banshees of Inisherin, which was absolutely wonderful. Very darkly funny meditation on masculinity and loneliness.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Watched the latest Jacob Geller video on Sekiro, which was really interesting.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-29</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-29</id>
        <published>2022-10-29T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Really chill day! The party finished quite late so I slept in!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went to the farm with someone I&amp;#39;m dating — and saw some piglets!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;My friend came to visit, I don&amp;#39;t see her too often so it was really nice just to catch up.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-28</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-28</id>
        <published>2022-10-28T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Nice day at work, quite busy but generally productive and not too stressful.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Cooked dinner with someone I&amp;#39;m dating, we made vegan fajitas!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went to a Halloween party, which was really lovely!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-27</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-27</id>
        <published>2022-10-27T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I did a spin class today, always makes me feel strong after!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went and got a pizza with someone I&amp;#39;m dating, very chill, good vibes all round.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went to a WARGASM/Scene Queen gig, supports went hard too. Great night!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-26</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-26</id>
        <published>2022-10-26T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Another productive and fun day at work today, got some good stuff done.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had dinner and watched TV with someone I&amp;#39;m dating, really lovely time!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went for a walk at lunch and got some air. It was lovely to take that time out of my day.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-25</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-25</id>
        <published>2022-10-25T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Lots of progress made on my visualisation piece at work, things are coming along nicely there.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I made a delicious dinner, oven-roasted vegetables and beans with a mustard dressing. I love taking the time to cook for myself.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Watched the first two episodes of the new season of Chucky. Very gay, super fun. I love this show! Also free on YouTube for anyone in the US/with a VPN (the first two, anyway).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-24</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-24</id>
        <published>2022-10-24T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Very relaxed but productive return to normal work, I made good progress.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had dinner with someone I&amp;#39;m dating. It&amp;#39;s nice to just relax and take stock after a long busy week.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Counselling today was extremely emotionally taxing, but overall pretty positive. I feel like I got one new understanding out of it, which is good.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-23</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-23</id>
        <published>2022-10-23T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went to the Turner Contemporary, which was an awesome space with some interesting exhibitions going on at the moment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a great breakfast and watched a storm rage over the sea. Beautiful.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Now I&amp;#39;m home, having some dinner and watching TV. It&amp;#39;s been a great busy week and it&amp;#39;s been lovely to just relax tonight.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-22</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-22</id>
        <published>2022-10-22T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Day 1 of my lovely holiday, went and got delicious seitan satay for breakfast with someone I&amp;#39;m dating. Great start to the day.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Walked on the beach and saw a crab!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went to the Margate Crab Museum, which was such a cool queer anti-capitalist space full of funny little displays and chill people.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-21</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-21</id>
        <published>2022-10-21T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Completed my residential training and got some really positive feedback about my presentation skills, as well as things to work on.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Spent some time with the other attendees talking — I feel like I&amp;#39;ve met some really cool, smart people these past three days.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Travelled home and to my holiday destination!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-20</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-20</id>
        <published>2022-10-20T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Day 2 of the residential was super productive. We completed a pitch deck together as a team, I had some moments to try my presenting skills, and I had some good snacks too.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Breakfast was really chilled and relaxed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had an early night and relaxed after a long day of work. It&amp;#39;s good to take time to actually recover.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-19</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-19</id>
        <published>2022-10-19T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Day 1 of my residential course at a beautiful chateau in France. The people are lovely, even if the material is super challenging.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I took an hour to walk around the lake here and take some photographs. It&amp;#39;s so beautiful, especially in autumn.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a call with someone I&amp;#39;m dating in the evening which was really lovely.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-18</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-18</id>
        <published>2022-10-18T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Productive morning at work, not much to say other than I got some pieces wrapped up and communicated some needs to my team. They&amp;#39;re really helpful.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I travelled to Paris for a residential course, which is really exciting. Can&amp;#39;t wait to get started.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a drink and got to know the people here. Everyone seems really friendly, no big egos or rudeness, just genuine and authentic.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-17</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-17</id>
        <published>2022-10-17T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Good day at work preparing for a big course.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Continued BSL course, going well.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Lovely date with someone, went to see Decision To Leave.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-16</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-16</id>
        <published>2022-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Breakfast, pancakes, with someone I&amp;#39;m dating and my parents.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Travel home was lovely - more crosswords, and some podcasts.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Started a British Sign Language course.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-15</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-15</id>
        <published>2022-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Travelled down to see my family, and did crosswords on the train.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Lovely day celebrating my nephew&amp;#39;s first birthday.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;A walk and dinner with someone I&amp;#39;m dating.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-14</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-14</id>
        <published>2022-10-14T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Chill morning, had some coffee and toast and listened to the latest Knowledge Fight about the Alex Jones judgement.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a work event which was really fun, got to meet some new people and hang out with folks on the project that I rarely see in person. Good times! I don&amp;#39;t think I&amp;#39;ve ever enjoyed a work event before!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Heading home to one of the people I&amp;#39;m dating, chill evening in and some dinner.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-13</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-13</id>
        <published>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Super productive and fun day at work, doing some kinda boring stuff but with nice people. Honestly it makes all the difference.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a chill evening in, tidied round and got packed for the weekend.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;An intense, sweaty and kind of emotional spin ride — it&amp;#39;s important to remember that my body has so many positives, including power and endurance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-12</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-12</id>
        <published>2022-10-12T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Pretty good day at work, made a good start on quite an involved task and did some training that needed doing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I cooked dinner with someone I&amp;#39;m dating, then we played boardgames and chilled out. Lovely evening.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Alex Jones got hit with $1B in damages. Couldn&amp;#39;t have happened to a nicer person. Get fucked.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-11</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-11</id>
        <published>2022-10-11T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I did a cardio boxing class, which was really fun and different, and did my back stretches too. Feels good to move my body around.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I listened to a bunch of good music — including the &lt;i&gt;Hedwig&lt;/i&gt; soundtrack because I&amp;#39;m gay — and got some housework done.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Today was a pretty challenging day at work, but I got through it and feel pretty good. I don&amp;#39;t have to absolutely crush every day — it&amp;#39;s okay just to get through it sometimes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-10</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-10</id>
        <published>2022-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a pretty good day at work, got some pieces done that needed doing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Used my spin bike for a bit — trying to get in the habit of regular exercise at the moment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a really nice long chat with someone I&amp;#39;m dating on the phone, which was lovely. We finalised some plans. Just a lovely way to spend time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-09</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-09</id>
        <published>2022-10-09T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a lovely lunch with someone: went to the park, chill little walk.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Cooked dinner with someone I&amp;#39;m dating, really delicious food and lovely company!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Watched &lt;i&gt;Hedwig and the Angry Inch&lt;/i&gt; for the first time, gorgeously weird and queer movie with great music and some of the most beautiful cinematography. Highly recommended.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-08</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-08</id>
        <published>2022-10-08T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a chill day with someone I&amp;#39;m dating, hanging out and making plans for the month.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Lovely dinner, sushi, as well as leftover soup turned into noodles for lunch.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Watched a bunch of &lt;i&gt;Pottery Throwdown&lt;/i&gt; with someone, which was lovely.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-07</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-07</id>
        <published>2022-10-07T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Tough but good day at work, got a difficult and awkward piece finished off.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Lovely evening with someone I&amp;#39;m dating.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Made a really delicious Thai butternut squash soup for dinner.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-06</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-06</id>
        <published>2022-10-06T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had my first therapy session today, the psychologist was really nice. Kind of tiring and difficult, but positive.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went on the exercise bike for half an hour! Let&amp;#39;s go!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Chatted with someone I&amp;#39;m dating on text, which was lovely post-counselling.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-05</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-05</id>
        <published>2022-10-05T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went on a date with a lovely person — we had dinner and saw &lt;i&gt;Flux Gourmet&lt;/i&gt;, which was excellent.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Work was good.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Offered some support to my friend who&amp;#39;s struggling at the moment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-04</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-04</id>
        <published>2022-10-04T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Got my medication sorted out, which has needed doing for a while.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Cooked a delicious tandoori aubergine curry with rice and some spicy pickle.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Watched some TV, had a chill evening tidying round and sitting on the sofa.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-03</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-03</id>
        <published>2022-10-03T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a very productive day at work, still feeling capable and like I know what I&amp;#39;m doing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Finished early to get a haircut. My last haircut was a pretty crappy experience but the hairdresser was really lovely and welcoming, and I feel really confident about how I look.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had an evening with a lovely person, just hung out, listened to music and had dinner together.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-02</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-02</id>
        <published>2022-10-02T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a coffee and a chill little morning with someone I&amp;#39;m dating, really sweet way to start the day.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Put on some eyeliner :)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I replayed &lt;i&gt;ANATOMY&lt;/i&gt; by Kitty Horrorshow today to get in a Hallowe&amp;#39;en mood, and that sure is still a video game. Geez. My poor mind.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-10-01</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-10-01</id>
        <published>2022-10-01T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-10-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a really chill morning having breakfast and coffee with a lovely person. Great start to the day — so chill my brain thought it must be Sunday!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;My friend is celebrating a big milestone in their sobriety, so we had a really fun party and I hung out with and got to know some cool folks. We also went to see some stand up, which was hilarious.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had an Almdudler, which I haven&amp;#39;t had in probably five years. Reminds me of being 12!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-30</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-30</id>
        <published>2022-09-30T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Super productive day at work, I got a lot done in a short span of time. I&amp;#39;m definitely susceptible to imposter syndrome but today was not one of those days.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a really chilled out day with a lovely person, we pet some animals and had lunch together. Just an all-round pleasant time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went out to dinner with my other lovely person to an Indian restaurant: the food was amazing, one of the best meals out I&amp;#39;ve had this year and that&amp;#39;s saying something.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-29</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-29</id>
        <published>2022-09-29T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a lovely date evening in a queer space, one of the most pleasant and supportive places I&amp;#39;ve been. Genuinely wonderful.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Good day at work, got a lot done but still took time for a nice lunch.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Listened to some chill music, including the new DCFC album.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-28</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-28</id>
        <published>2022-09-28T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I started The Turn of the Screw: I&amp;#39;m not really a &amp;#34;seasonal reader&amp;#34;, but I make an exception for Hallowe&amp;#39;en. I love a ghost story. I had seen a little of The Haunting of Bly Manor — it&amp;#39;s interesting to see what they chose to change&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had a really nice lunch. There&amp;#39;s a university café that I&amp;#39;ve been going to semi-regularly: they don&amp;#39;t always have vegan food, but when they do it&amp;#39;s usually excellent.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I did my meditation, something I&amp;#39;m trying to stay consistent with. It makes me feel better, more centered, disproportionately often: [investor voice] it has high positive EV.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-27</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-27</id>
        <published>2022-09-27T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a phone chat with a lovely person, I love talking on the phone. So underrated.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Reading some Borges, who I&amp;#39;ve discovered is a silly weirdo who writes funny stories. Why did no-one tell me this? This often happens with authors I perceive as &amp;#34;hard&amp;#34; — Moby Dick was the same, just a fun book about a silly gay whaler.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a pretty good day at work, mostly calls and organisational metawork but still very important.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-26</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-26</id>
        <published>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I finished &lt;a href=&#34;/books/non-fiction/in-the-dream-house.html&#34;&gt;In The Dream House&lt;/a&gt; today — brilliant and utterly devastating. I also started &lt;i&gt;Fictions&lt;/i&gt;, I haven&amp;#39;t read Borges before and I&amp;#39;m loving his style. Good book day today.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went to get laser hair removal, and had a lovely walk home afterwards. The city looks so lovely in this weather. I love this time of year.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Called to arrange my first counselling session, very positive.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-25</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-25</id>
        <published>2022-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had a very productive morning, did some house and food shopping then meditated. Lovely morning walking weather.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had a really nice lunch, roasted vegetables with kombucha tofu sausage. Have a lot of left-over veggies in the fridge now.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went for a really gorgeous autumnal walk and took some cool photos of my old church. Lento 10/10 camera app.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-24</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-24</id>
        <published>2022-09-24T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got &lt;i&gt;Tetris Effect&lt;/i&gt; on sale and played a bit of that — very cool, fun sound design.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went for a walk and found a little cafe that I might go to tomorrow morning.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I did some meditation, which turned into a nap. Today was really difficult, but I am trying to allow myself space and time to recover.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-23</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-23</id>
        <published>2022-09-23T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I am feeling really ill today, but put my physical health above obligations and stayed in tonight. Not gonna pretend I&amp;#39;m not disappointed but it was the right thing to do.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Got a new City PB, I&amp;#39;m still having so much fun with Celeste.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Work was really good today, we wrapped up a big section. Time for something new&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-22</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-22</id>
        <published>2022-09-22T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Despite the stressful start, work was really good today. I got some interesting little bits of coding done and delivered some value.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had breakfast and coffee with a lovely person. Starting the day with people you really care for is such a pleasant experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went out for a work meal at a really good Spanish place, everyone was lovely to be around. Just a good day all round.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-21</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-21</id>
        <published>2022-09-21T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Super productive day at work, I got those two pieces finished up and handing in. Also had some good conversations about the next things I&amp;#39;m working on.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Lovely evening with a lovely person, we made dinner together and watched TV. I have a very social week so it was nice to just chill out. We also had a good talk and I was honest with myself and them.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Did some more self-care-type tasks: body stuff, tidying. Things that improve my mood long-term but that I don&amp;#39;t enjoy doing in the moment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-20</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-20</id>
        <published>2022-09-20T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Got a new any% PB, I&amp;#39;m having such a fun time just working on little bits of the game.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a really productive day at work, completing two pieces that needed doing. I feel very skilled at the moment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Did some self-care tasks, including things I always skip and always help my mood.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-19</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-19</id>
        <published>2022-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Made some tentative plans to see lovely people this week.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Started playing the Arphimigon D-Sides, super fun and challenging. I&amp;#39;m going to work my way through those.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Due to national holiday I ended up shopping somewhere I don&amp;#39;t normally, and I got a baguette which was actually really delicious! Had a great lunch and dinner.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-18</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-18</id>
        <published>2022-09-18T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Took the day to rest and recuperate, something I should try harder to prioritise more. But I guess &amp;#34;prioritisation&amp;#34; goes against the point of &amp;#34;rest&amp;#34;, huh?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been really getting back into running &lt;i&gt;Celeste&lt;/i&gt; recently — got a new PB on City and spent some time working on Chapter 6 &amp;amp; 7 any% routes. I think I&amp;#39;m making progress!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Chatted to some friends on messaging apps for a bit. Today was a very &amp;#34;inside&amp;#34; day, which isn&amp;#39;t my favourite, but it turned out pretty good.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-17</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-17</id>
        <published>2022-09-17T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Got a 44:54 today, sub-45 achieved! What next?! Who knows?!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I fixed the flush in my bathroom, always feels rewarding to do house maintenance. Something to remember.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Made a really nice broth for lunch.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-16</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-16</id>
        <published>2022-09-16T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I decided to go for a sub-45 in &lt;i&gt;Celeste&lt;/i&gt; any%, and got a new PB of 45:43 on my second serious run. I&amp;#39;ve completely got this.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Made plans to go on holiday in October — and to see a lot of people next week!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had a sinus headache today, so trying be kind to myself. Ate good food, wrapped up warm, and rested. Making a conscious effort not to shame myself for resting and recovering. On the plus side — I got a cold, it&amp;#39;s officially autumn!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-15</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-15</id>
        <published>2022-09-15T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had breakfast with a person, coffee and chill times in the morning. Great start to the day.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I started learning the spike jump and double wall bounce in 4A — wow, spike jumps are easy! I always thought they were way outside my skillset!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I bought a really cute fancy jumpsuit for a work do next week. I&amp;#39;m not the most &amp;#34;trad fancy clothing&amp;#34;, but it&amp;#39;s nice to dress fancy sometimes!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-14</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-14</id>
        <published>2022-09-14T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had dinner &amp;amp; a chill night in with a lovely person — we made broth and dumplings and watched &lt;i&gt;National Treasure&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;My in-person counselling was signed off by the insurer, so I&amp;#39;ll hopefully be starting that soon!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I learnt 2 new skips in &lt;i&gt;Celeste&lt;/i&gt;: a spike jump in 5B that I probably won&amp;#39;t use in runs, and another spike jump in 7A that I definitely will!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-13</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-13</id>
        <published>2022-09-13T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had a nice oat milk chocolate bar at lunch.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;My work have sorted out a laptop for me, it&amp;#39;s taken them a while but that should make my workflow a lot easier.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a really fun evening, got dinner with a lovely person, met some of her friends and went to a stand-up gig.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-12</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-12</id>
        <published>2022-09-12T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Got a lot of work done, including some stuff that I don&amp;#39;t think anyone else would&amp;#39;ve looked at yet. Hopefully has value.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I &amp;#34;did self-care&amp;#34;: meditated, went for a run, and did my stretches. I had a good lunch, too. Trying to make time for myself.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I&amp;#39;m going to eat some pizza and watch videos, just relax tonight.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-11</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-11</id>
        <published>2022-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a nice relaxed late breakfast — cooked vegan breakfast with coffee and lemonade.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had a phone call with one of my friends, it was good to just chat and catch up.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went round for dinner and boardgames with someone, really lovely evening after a pretty busy weekend.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-10</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-10</id>
        <published>2022-09-10T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;We got donuts and coffee for breakfast and hung out with some animals!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went to a street food market and got arepas and sushi — odd combo, but both really tasty.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went to two parties: a housewarming/birthday that was so lovely and chill and welcoming, and a birthday at a cool metal bar where I did some dancing!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-09</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-09</id>
        <published>2022-09-09T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Good day at work - long but all positive. Got some stuff done.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went out for dinner and had a delicious thali.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went mudlarking with a lovely person — we found some bones and pottery fragments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-08</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-08</id>
        <published>2022-09-08T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Met a bunch of people from my project in person, and went for coffee with the person I work most closely with — everyone is so nice.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Spoke to my medical insurer about in-person counselling, which they&amp;#39;ve signed off on. Hopefully a positive step for my mental wellbeing, despite how much the initial call shook me.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went to my self-defense class, which was really fun — we did a takedown and lots of punching!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-07</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-07</id>
        <published>2022-09-07T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Got a couple of cheap USB thumbsticks and loaded them up with files to share with friends and loved ones.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I&amp;#39;ve had a stiff back for a couple of days, so I took time to do stretches and that&amp;#39;s really eased it off — maybe something I should do more often?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Read a couple of zines/essays on anarchism and polyamory, &lt;a href=&#34;https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/susan-song-polyamory-and-queer-anarchism-infinite-possibilities-for-resistance&#34;&gt;Polyamory and Queer Anarchism&lt;/a&gt; is a good theoretical primer to go with the emotion and practice of &lt;a href=&#34;https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/andie-nordgren-the-short-instructional-manifesto-for-relationship-anarchy&#34;&gt;Nordgren&lt;/a&gt; . I&amp;#39;ve been loving the Anarchist Library recently!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-06</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-06</id>
        <published>2022-09-06T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Good day at work today, got some positive feedback on what I&amp;#39;ve done so far. Lots of calls though so I&amp;#39;m pretty tired!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went to the post office to pick up coffee for this month — excited to try a cup tomorrow.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;The first three months of prints from &lt;a href=&#34;https://ritualdust.com/works/print/henbane/&#34;&gt;Ritual Dust&amp;#39;s print club&lt;/a&gt; arrived today! They&amp;#39;re each absolutely gorgeous, I hope they inspire me to find beauty in my day.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-05</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-05</id>
        <published>2022-09-05T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got the grade back for the second data visualisation, and I passed!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a moment where I was feeling quite low, but I spoke to a friend and it really helped.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Read a bunch of cool pamphlets and zines, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mary-nardini-gang-toward-the-queerest-insurrection&#34;&gt;&lt;i&gt;Towards the queerest insurrection&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-04</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-04</id>
        <published>2022-09-04T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Got brunch with one of the lovely people in my life and had a super pleasant chill morning.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went to the anarchist bookshop and picked up a ton of cool zines.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a fun evening at a queer housewarming/BBQ with the other lovely person I&amp;#39;m seeing, met loads of cool people.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-03</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-03</id>
        <published>2022-09-03T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I watched &lt;a href=&#34;https://invidious.fdn.fr/watch?v=mcYztBmf_y8&#34;&gt;the latest Jacob Geller video&lt;/a&gt; , super interesting — it reminded me of conversations I had about therapy, productivity and work with a friend.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I took time to do some chores: prepped some lunch for tomorrow, tidied and dusted, and wiped down the kitchen.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I&amp;#39;m going on a date tonight, we&amp;#39;re seeing &lt;i&gt;Three Thousand Years of Longing&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-02</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-02</id>
        <published>2022-09-02T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Played some more &lt;i&gt;Thumper&lt;/i&gt; and got to the last stage — this and &lt;i&gt;Celeste&lt;/i&gt; are the perfect combination for me: high difficulty, lovely gamefeel and quick feedback.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got the first piece of actual work done for my project!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I finalised my weekend plans with lovely people!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-09-01</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-09-01</id>
        <published>2022-09-01T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-09-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had a delicious lunch, went for a walk, and bought some cursed chewing gum (raspberry and vanilla flavour).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I opted for more old-school tech today: neon pink F91-W over a smartwatch, and my iPod for music. It did really well! Couple of minor memory problems but nothing a reboot couldn&amp;#39;t fix.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went to my queer self-defense class and got a drink with them after — everyone is so lovely and fun.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-31</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-31</id>
        <published>2022-08-31T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I got a really pleasant big day planner, which hopefully should help me function a bit better day-to-day.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Played some more &lt;i&gt;Thumper&lt;/i&gt;, finished level 6 which has some really tough sections at the end.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Made some time to read after work — I&amp;#39;ve started reading &lt;a href=&#34;https://biggsrbr.weebly.com/uploads/8/7/4/4/8744974/the-tao-of-pooh-by-benjamin-hoff1.pdf&#34;&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Tao of Pooh&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt; as part of my intermittent Le Guin-inspired Taoism reading.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-30</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-30</id>
        <published>2022-08-30T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;First day of my new project at work — had loads of intro calls with people and went through some handover, it went really well!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went to a farm for lunch and said hi to all the animals.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Watched &lt;a href=&#34;https://invidious.fdn.fr/watch?v=isimXKxF7l0&#34;&gt;carrarium speedrunning &lt;i&gt;Celeste_ all cassettes&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; at _Flame Fatale&lt;/i&gt;, which was a super fun run — resisting the urge to learn a new category!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-29</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-29</id>
        <published>2022-08-29T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went for a ride on my bike and chilled in the park for a bit.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went round to my friend&amp;#39;s house and made pizza!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Started playing &lt;i&gt;Thumper&lt;/i&gt; which is fantastic, tough and immersive in like the real meaning of the word.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-28</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-28</id>
        <published>2022-08-28T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went out for breakfast with the family before I got the train home, had lots of coffee and some OJ.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Hung out with my baby nephew for a bit and ate some carrot cake.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Listened to music on the train home — the new Muse album, some Slayer and &lt;i&gt;Bimbocore&lt;/i&gt; by Scene Queen.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-27</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-27</id>
        <published>2022-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had pancakes for breakfast with someone lovely.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went out for dinner for my mum&amp;#39;s birthday, Thai food.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Hung out and played Mario Kart with my sister and her husband, saw my little nephew.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-26</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-26</id>
        <published>2022-08-26T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a great day at work.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Lovely date, very chill night in 🙂&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I fell over on a run and got a juicy bruise, but a couple lovely people came over and checked I was okay.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-25</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-25</id>
        <published>2022-08-25T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Ate really well today, lots of fruit and fresh foods, and I had tofu fried rice for dinner.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Really productive day at work, I got the first assignment for my Python course submitted.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Chatted some toki pona today and started expanding that part of the site (including a &lt;a href=&#34;/toki-pona/tenpo-ni/)&#34;&gt;journal&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-24</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-24</id>
        <published>2022-08-24T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a good day at work, got a lot done in the morning then had some intro calls for my new project.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went and had dinner with a friend who I haven&amp;#39;t seen in a while, which was lovely.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Made plans with someone lovely to go swimming 🙂&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-23</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-23</id>
        <published>2022-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a lovely date, went out for dinner then saw NOPE.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Started the next module on my Python course, which dives into data visualisation (and ethics!!!)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Re-downloaded Discord and wrote some toki pona for the first time in a while.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-22</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-22</id>
        <published>2022-08-22T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Did some yoga this morning - my back is almost back to normal!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Got out pens and paper to do some drawing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Organised some social and date nights for the rest of the week 🙂&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-21</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-21</id>
        <published>2022-08-21T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went for a walk through parks and churchyards, saw some anti-fascist art and interesting buildings.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I did some yoga to ease my back off and re-centre myself, it really helped. I should do it more often.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I had a coffee and a read, starting the Tao Te Ching and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cunning-folk.com/read-posts/the-air-issue&#34;&gt;Air issue of Cunning Folk zine&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-20</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-20</id>
        <published>2022-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went for a walk to ease my back off and picked up some cool zines from an independent bookshop.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Started watching Revolutionary Girl Utena 🌹&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;The weather was really nice today, it&amp;#39;s finally started to cool down.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-19</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-19</id>
        <published>2022-08-19T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I finished the final assignment for my Python course and got started on something else.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Listened to some really good music including the new Mountain Goats album, think I may need to revive the shortly lived music zine.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I did some stretches for my back and made a lot of time to rest.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-18</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-18</id>
        <published>2022-08-18T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a super productive work day, got lots of required stuff done and some more Python learning.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Played some badminton and met up with friends (and tweaked my back 😭)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;One of my family members had some minor surgery and it went well, just wonderful news!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-17</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-17</id>
        <published>2022-08-17T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a lovely date, we ate dinner, plantain and vegan BBQ, and went to see Bullet Train.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Work was long but good, I got a lot done and learnt some new pandas tricks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;My hair looked good!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-16</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-16</id>
        <published>2022-08-16T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Did week 2 of the Python course — sea legs, got.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Met a couple of the other newbies and had a chat. It was really nice, what I missed out with online induction.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I went for a walk and had a good lunch.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-15</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-15</id>
        <published>2022-08-15T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Tough mental health day, but called a friend: talking to her helped take my mind off things.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I did the first week(!) of a Python data science course to get my sea legs again.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Made a really nice dinner.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-14</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-14</id>
        <published>2022-08-14T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Reached out to someone to tell him I got a lot from an article he wrote.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Picked up my medication, which is lucky because I just ran out.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Logged in and did a bit of the CBT course.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-13</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-13</id>
        <published>2022-08-13T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Bought some gorgeous art and had a chat with one of the artists about demons 🎨&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went out for breakfast, pancakes with some coffee and OJ 🍊&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Messaged some people and started making social plans 🙂&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-12</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-12</id>
        <published>2022-08-12T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Made quesadillas, they turned out really well considering I&amp;#39;ve never made them before! 🌶️&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Played some Terraforming Mars and got my ass absolutely handed to me 😂&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Did a bit of work on the website 🖥️&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-11</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-11</id>
        <published>2022-08-11T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went for my laser appointment, it&amp;#39;s going well and the tech was really lovely 🙂&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Nice busy day at work 💻&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Got Syncthing working, backing up my photos out of the Google environment 👍&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-10</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-10</id>
        <published>2022-08-10T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a really nice breakfast with fresh strawberries and strong coffee 🍓&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Spoke to my sister on the phone 🙂&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Took some time out of my day to do yoga, which was very centering 🌞&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-09</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-09</id>
        <published>2022-08-09T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Got a lot of the rote mandatory training done so hopefully the rest of my week will be more interesting 🙂&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went to a life-drawing class with a lovely person 🎨&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I ate really good vegan food, peanut butter vegetable curry and a burger with rosemary fries 🍔&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-08</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-08</id>
        <published>2022-08-08T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;First day at my new job, I got started on all my induction tasks and met my new manager 🙂&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went for a walk in the evening before the sun set 🌇&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I cooked a good dinner, roasted veg and spicy tempeh 🥕&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-07</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-07</id>
        <published>2022-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Started moving my website over to handwritten HTML, including a journal page to hold my Three Good Things 💻&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Finished my lemon painting 🖌&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Saw a friend and got delicious food together 🍔&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-06</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-06</id>
        <published>2022-08-06T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I dialed in the new coffee and had a couple of espressos - really tasty with a strong strawberry smell 🍓&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I moved my website over to using Atkinson Hyperlegible, which I really like the look of and is allegedly very readable 💻&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Started an acrylic painting of my lemon bowl 🍋&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-05</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-05</id>
        <published>2022-08-05T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I ordered coffee from a local roaster that I believe to be a more ethical bunch, and it arrived today! Can&amp;#39;t wait to try it ☕&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Did some impromptu testing of the NHS gender identity clinic&amp;#39;s self-referral page and submitted a bug report for dead links 😂&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Made plans with friends and dates for the next week, and updated my diary and calendar too 📆&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-04</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-04</id>
        <published>2022-08-04T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Went to the library to return some books, and got out &amp;#34;The Word for World is Forest&amp;#34; by Ursula K. Le Guin 📖&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a friendly and helpful chat with my mental health supporter about the CBT app I&amp;#39;ll use 🧠&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Got the IT kit from the job I start on Monday, as well as a snazzy little backpack. Someone on the team reached out too!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-03</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-03</id>
        <published>2022-08-03T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I&amp;#39;m feeling even better than yesterday, on the mend 👍&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Made some plans with a lovely person for when I&amp;#39;m well ☺️&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a lovely call with my parents. I wasn&amp;#39;t able to see them recently so it was nice to just chat&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-02</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-02</id>
        <published>2022-08-02T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I watched some of the Alex Jones trial, the parents&amp;#39; testimony was deeply moving. I&amp;#39;m glad they get to hold him accountable.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I feel way better today, still not 100% definitely but moving in the right direction 🤒&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Had a cathartic sob listening to She/Her/Hers, &lt;a href=&#34;https://sheherhers.bandcamp.com/album/planet-of-weeds-ep&#34;&gt;Planet of Weeds&lt;/a&gt; . Beautiful sad track about the fear and dread of losing everything beautiful in the world 🌳&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-08-01</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-08-01</id>
        <published>2022-08-01T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I&amp;#39;m feeling really run down, but people have sent get-well-soon messages 🥰&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I started The Haunting of Bly Manor which is excellent 🏳️‍🌈&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I checked in with my friend who&amp;#39;s moved, I really miss them 🙂&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-07-31</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-07-31</id>
        <published>2022-07-31T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-07-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I have a lovely date ☺️&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I figured out why my water pressure wasn&amp;#39;t great and fixed it, then had a shower 🚿&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I wore an outfit that made me feel hot 🔥&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022-07-30</title>
        <id>https://hd-dn.com/three-good-things/#2022-07-30</id>
        <published>2022-07-30T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-07-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Breakfast and coffee with a lovely person, deeply pleasant start to the day ☕&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I bought a fruit bowl and filled it with lemons to put in my water 🍋&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;I opened a really nice orange wine🍷&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
    </entry>
</feed>